<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516174500 -0400" stop="20260516183000 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>Monk must confront his prejudice against nudists when he's called to investigate a murder on a nude beach.</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk and the Naked Man</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516180858 -0400" stop="20260516183324 -0400"><title>Superstore</title><desc>Store manager Glenn gets overly excited when the Cloud 9 corporate magazine, Stratus, is interested in a story. The reporter, Cynthia, is more focused on Jonah, however, and the two develop a more-than-business relationship, which Amy had suspected. Garrett does his best to avoid be photographed for the magazine's cover. Cheyenne asks her boyfriend, Bo, to come up with a corporate jingle to help earn money to pay expenses for their upcoming baby.</desc><sub-title>Magazine Profile</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516174358 -0400" stop="20260516192446 -0400"><title>Clerks II</title><desc>A calamity at Dante and Randal's shops sends them looking for new horizons, but they ultimately settle at Mooby's, a fictional fast-food restaurant. Free from his dead-end job and lodged in a new one, Dante begins to break free of his rut, planning to move away with his clingy fianc&#233;e. He is ready to leave the horrors of minimum-wage New Jersey behind, but Randal, always the more hostile of the two, starts to become overwhelmed by his own rancor.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260516230000 +0100" stop="20260516233000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>A fleeing Shir&#333; is eventually cornered by Rin, who offers to spare his life if he gives her his Command Seals. However, he refuses, prompting Rin to try and kill him. Both are then distracted by a scream downstairs and he and Rin find an unconscious girl. As Rin attempts to heal her, a dagger flies through an open door, aimed for Rin, but Shir&#333; blocks it with his arm, wounding himself in the process. He runs outside to find the female Servant, which is of the Rider class, and repels an attack by her. Shir&#333; considers summoning Saber via Command Seal, but decides it is too risky to get her involved and resolves to confront Rider himself. Rider resumes her assault, and Shir&#333; is nearly killed by her until Rin rescues him. At Rin's home, Shir&#333; and Rin decide to form a temporary truce to find Rider's Master.</desc><sub-title>Two Magi (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516173600 -0400" stop="20260516183827 -0400"><title>Rivers with Griff Rhys Jones</title><desc>The actor explores the relationship between cities and rivers when he travels to London, examining how the Lea has played a vital role in its history, and discovering the balance between waste leaving a town and the water coming in. Griff also meets the community in Essex that grows Sicilian cucumbers, sails a gunpowder boat and trains with a team of veteran rowers</desc><sub-title>The Lea</sub-title></programme></tv>