<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517183000 -0400" stop="20260517190000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Tina goes too far trying to be a perfect mentor. Meanwhile, Bob and Linda test out the gym next door.</desc><sub-title>A Fish Called Tina</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517181042 -0400" stop="20260517184047 -0400"><title>Utopia (AU)</title><desc>Tony is forced to step in when an endangered grass threatens to derail plans for a new container terminal. Rhonda is convinced that the NBA needs a major overhaul of its website.</desc><sub-title>Protected Species</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517175744 -0400" stop="20260517191641 -0400"><title>The Cat Returns</title><desc>After helping a cat, a seventeen-year-old girl finds herself involuntarily engaged to a cat Prince in a magical world where her only hope of freedom lies with a dapper cat statuette come to life.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517231500 +0100" stop="20260517234500 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Ch. Insp. Conway wants to see P.C. Smith and W.P.C. Martella about a special assignment: going through the missing persons register and following up some of the cases. A cynical Sgt. Penny tells them the initiative is politicially-motivated. A woman who has been harassing her local MP about her missing daughter only wants her back so she can get a three bedroom house. The girl turns up dead. The wife of a missing man who has been onto the Chief Constable is found to have killed herself after seeing his ad in a lonely hearts magazine. Smith is quite excited about his new role, and is hoping to set up a specialised missing persons unit at Sun Hill, but as soon as the politically-sensitive cases are solved, Smith and Martella's unit is disbanded.</desc><sub-title>Loss</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517180936 -0400" stop="20260517190117 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>The team take another look at: salami rocket fuel, rough road driving, pottery record, tailgate up or down, and sword vs sword. Some retests are needed, and some went perfectly, but the fans had more questions.</desc><sub-title>More Myths Revisited</sub-title></programme></tv>