<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521043500 -0400" stop="20260521052000 -0400"><title>Buffy the Vampire Slayer</title><desc>As Harmony and her vampire gang plot Buffy's demise, Dawn adjusts to life with a Slayer.</desc><sub-title>Real Me</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521042928 -0400" stop="20260521045401 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Jake and Amy's ongoing bet about who can make more arrests comes to a close. Charles receives the Medal of Valor for getting shot in the line of duty, but the pain medication he is taking causes him to reveal his true opinions.</desc><sub-title>The Bet</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521042152 -0400" stop="20260521045911 -0400"><title>The Boy, the Mole, the Fox and the Horse</title><desc>Charlie Mackesy's bestselling book comes to life in this beautifully animated film from NoneMore and Bad Robot Productions. Follow the unlikely bond between four friends as they explore the meaning of kindness, friendship, courage and hope. A story for viewers of all ages in a heartwarming, classically animated film.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260521093500 +0100" stop="20260521100000 +0100"><title>Impractical Jokers</title><desc>The Jokers give each other humiliating tasks to complete on the mall escalator, ask absurd survey questions at the zoo, and are forced to whisper sweet nothings to grocery store patrons. Plus, tonight's losers are the surprise opening act for Imagine Dragons and must perform for 14,000 disappointed music fans.</desc><sub-title>Enter the Dragons</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521044731 -0400" stop="20260521053418 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>Mike tracks down a Lincoln Continental, which set new style standards for luxury sedans in the 1960s. But tastes have changed and Edd hatches a refurb plan.</desc><sub-title>Lincoln Continental</sub-title></programme></tv>