<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520103000 -0400" stop="20260520110000 -0400"><title>Frasier</title><desc>Frasier uses his father as a pawn in order to date the attractive owner of a home for senior citizens. Niles and Daphne plan a picnic during which they watch a meteor shower, but are accidentally separated at the crucial moment.</desc><sub-title>The Bad Son</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520101955 -0400" stop="20260520104406 -0400"><title>Community</title><desc>When Jeff loses his home and his car, he is forced to move into Abed's dorm room. Troy has a big date, but why is a jealous Annie trying to help? Meanwhile, Pierce becomes the keyboardist for Vaughn's band.</desc><sub-title>Home Economics</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260520095141 -0400" stop="20260520115051 -0400"><title>Children Who Chase Lost Voices</title><desc>A coming of age story involving young love and a mysterious music, coming from a crystal radio left as a memento by an absent father, that leads a young heroine deep into a hidden world.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520150000 +0100" stop="20260520160000 +0100"><title>The Chase (2009)</title><desc>Four people who have never met before - Rachael, Mollie, Howard and Alan - take on the Chaser. Bradley Walsh guides the contestants through a battle of wits in the hope that they'll go home with thousands of pounds.</desc><sub-title>Episode 125</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520094559 -0400" stop="20260520103802 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>The 120-seater Curry Lounge in Nottingham cost its owner, Raz, &#163;500,000. But, six months after opening, it's haemorrhaging &#163;3,000 a week. Maybe customers are put off by the decor, unkindly but accurately described by Gordon Ramsay as looking like the interior of a lap-dancing club. Raz has made a rod for his restaurant's back, thanks to the barmy idea of letting customers choose the make-up of their own curries. Yes, that's right, if you want a chicken and prawn korma, that's what you shall have. But such nonsense is draining and demoralising for the excellent kitchen staff, so Ramsay brings the Curry Lounge back to basics in one of the most satisfying Kitchen Nightmares of recent memory. Everyone is charming, so Ramsay doesn't need to bluster too much: he can get on with bringing his skill and common sense to bear on a restaurant that's about to run out of luck.</desc><sub-title>Curry Lounge</sub-title></programme></tv>