<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521073000 -0400" stop="20260521080000 -0400"><title>The King of Queens</title><desc>A bedridden Carrie gets Doug to team with Arthur for a shuffleboard tournament, but his skills aren't to Arthur's liking. Meanwhile, Carrie pretends to continue being sick so that Holly will continue to cook for her.</desc><sub-title>Icky Shuffle</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521073138 -0400" stop="20260521075617 -0400"><title>The Goldbergs (2013)</title><desc>Beverly runs into her enemy, Betsy Rubenstone; Murray and Adam try to rent a video but are forced to pay a late fee.</desc><sub-title>The Other Smother</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521071108 -0400" stop="20260521085454 -0400"><title>The Lego Movie</title><desc>The LEGO Movie is a 3D animated film which follows lead character, Emmet, a completely ordinary LEGO mini-figure who is identified as the most "extraordinary person" and the key to saving the Lego universe. Emmet and his friends go on an epic journey to stop the evil tyrant, Lord Business.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260521120000 +0100" stop="20260521130000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Momma Cherri's Soul Food Shack has hit ROCK BOTTOM.

It's sounds SO GOOD: an intimate 40-seater a stone's throw from Brighton's sea front with loads of hungry locals and a steady stream of tourists. Big soul momma, owner Charita Jones produces a menu of irresistibly unique classics from the Deep South.

Should be a surefire MONEYSPINNER, right?

Wrong... the shack is in a hole... a very deep FINANCIAL HOLE.

Despite three and a half years of hard graft it's a SPLITTING HEADACHE of a cafe.

The food's hard to fault but the punters are nowhere to be seen, Head Chef Brian and a rag-tag collection of part-timers are taking the mickey - and despite working a seven-day week Charita's got an empty restaurant and owes the bank &#163;65,000. If ever there was a case of too many cooks, this is it. Charita's a natural, but she's never made a profit on the restaurant and is now facing financial disaster.

It's time to get SERIOUS... else the Soul Food Shack is finished.

Can Gordon successfully shut her out o</desc><sub-title>Momma Cherri's Soul Food Shack</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521073958 -0400" stop="20260521083252 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 23</sub-title></programme></tv>