<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521103000 -0400" stop="20260521110000 -0400"><title>Frasier</title><desc>Frasier hires a butler to take over for Daphne's housekeeping duties, now that she is Niles' girlfriend. However, Mel continues to forbid them to be seen in public, and when she unexpectedly shows up at a party at Frasier's house and ruins Niles and Daphne's planned evening out, it proves to be the last straw.</desc><sub-title>Taking Liberties</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521102327 -0400" stop="20260521105605 -0400"><title>Last Week Tonight with John Oliver</title><desc>The vast majority of US judges are elected, forcing many judges to pander to the electorate and accept campaign money in order to keep their jobs. This seems slightly troubling... 

The UK's Labour Party has painted a campaign van pink in an attempt to attract women voters. We are glad they didn't keep going with that strategy.</desc><sub-title>Elected Judges</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521102543 -0400" stop="20260521120536 -0400"><title>Elf</title><desc>When young Buddy falls into Santa's gift sack on Christmas Eve, he's transported back to the North Pole and raised as a toy-making elf by Santa's helpers. But as he grows into adulthood, he can't shake the nagging feeling that he doesn't belong. Buddy vows to visit Manhattan and find his real dad, a workaholic.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260521150000 +0100" stop="20260521160000 +0100"><title>The Chase (2009)</title><desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as four strangers - Ronnie, Faye, Ben and Paula - come together in the hope that they can take on the Chaser as a team and leave with thousands of pounds. Who will they be in battle against in this episode?</desc><sub-title>Episode 126</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521104414 -0400" stop="20260521113726 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 24</sub-title></programme></tv>