<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521014500 -0400" stop="20260521023000 -0400"><title>Stargate SG-1</title><desc>SG-1 helps to evacuate the Tok'ra to a new base -- but matters are complicated when a spy reveals their location to Apophis. The team attempts a daring plan to take out the Goa'uld's powerful fleet.</desc><sub-title>Exodus (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521013546 -0400" stop="20260521020017 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>It's Valentine's Day, and the TGS crew is celebrating by pulling an all nighter to put together a new episode. While Pete completely forgets the holiday, Kenneth and Cerie may be starting an office romance. Meanwhile, Liz wonders if Dennis is back in her life after she receives flowers from a secret admirer and newly divorced Jack wants to party with Tracy, who for once wants to spend a night alone with his wife instead.</desc><sub-title>Up All Night</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521001652 -0400" stop="20260521020224 -0400"><title>Ponyo</title><desc>When Sosuke, a young boy who lives on a clifftop overlooking the sea, rescues a stranded goldfish named Ponyo, he discovers more than he bargained for. Ponyo is a curious, energetic young creature who yearns to be human, but even as she causes chaos around the house, her father, a powerful sorcerer, schemes to return Ponyo to the sea.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260521063000 +0100" stop="20260521070000 +0100"><title>My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic</title><desc>When the CMC's figure out that Big Mac has his first crush, they vow to help him win Sugar Belle's heart against the competition of Feather Bangs.</desc><sub-title>Hard to Say Anything</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521014333 -0400" stop="20260521023014 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Actors Anthony Anderson and Marsai Martin ("Black-ish) face off in a series of games with host Keegan-Michael Key.</desc><sub-title>Kids vs. Adults</sub-title></programme></tv>