<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260526014500 -0400" stop="20260526023000 -0400"><title>Stargate SG-1</title><desc>After a rough ride through the stargate to P39-865, the sun of that planet turns red. Carter deduces that an override of stargate protocols allowed them to create a wormhole through the sun, starting a reaction that will cause the sun to die. SG-1 must now make up for their mistake or P39-865 will become incapable of supporting life.</desc><sub-title>Red Sky</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260526014530 -0400" stop="20260526021115 -0400"><title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title><desc>Mac teams up with Frank and Charlie to create a public access newscast after he misses his chance at fame in the news. Meanwhile, Dennis and Dee try to make it big in the club scene.</desc><sub-title>Frank Sets Sweet Dee On Fire</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260526002923 -0400" stop="20260526020318 -0400"><title>Trolls World Tour</title><desc>Queen Poppy and Branch make a surprising discovery &#8212; there are other Troll worlds beyond their own, and their distinct differences create big clashes between these various tribes. When a mysterious threat puts all of the Trolls across the land in danger, Poppy, Branch, and their band of friends must embark on an epic quest to create harmony among the feuding Trolls to unite them against certain doom.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260526014120 -0400" stop="20260526020912 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>It's the final day and the B&amp;B hosts gather for one last time to find out how much they've been paid. Unfortunately some of the hosts find their emotions running away with them.</desc><sub-title>Payment Day, Week 12</sub-title></programme></tv>