<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522174500 -0400" stop="20260522183000 -0400"><title>Bones</title><desc>In the season finale, a dead body is found at a club called "The Lab." The team has to do some unexpected and unusual things that have to do with this club. Brennan and Booth may become a couple.</desc><sub-title>The End in the Beginning</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522181105 -0400" stop="20260522183351 -0400"><title>Everybody Hates Chris</title><desc>Julius finds $200 in food stamps but Rochelle is too embarassed to let Sheila see them, so she dips into the family savings while at the store. This leads to trouble at home when Julius has all kinds of ideas on how they can spend the cash they saved by using the stamps.

Elsewhere, Chris and Greg fall out over a school science project.</desc><sub-title>Everybody Hates Food Stamps</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522173745 -0400" stop="20260522191907 -0400"><title>WALL&#183;E</title><desc>A robot who is responsible for cleaning a waste-covered Earth meets another robot and falls in love with her. Together, they set out on a journey that will alter the fate of mankind.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522230000 +0100" stop="20260522233000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>CID are keeping an eye on a man who is suspected of illegal shipment of arms to 3rd world countries.  No one has been able to make a case against him in 8 years.  A package gets delivered that could be for the suspect.  A car is parked in the carpark overnight and it turns out to be the missing car Yorkie is dealing with.  As the couple turn the key it explodes.   Yorkie tries to explain to a couple 12 days after their car was nicked, that the chances of getting it back are low but he has no objection to them looking for it.</desc><sub-title>Free Wheel</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522173012 -0400" stop="20260522181801 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>With memory, things are not always as they seem: Details go missing, recollections change, and sometimes our brains fill in the blanks and create false visual memories. Our experts are on a mission to find out where memories reside in the brain by examining every millimeter for clues. Investigating every piece of the memory puzzle, from how we recognize faces even if they have been digitally distorted to how we can move memories from short-term to long-term storage.</desc><sub-title>Remember This!</sub-title></programme></tv>