<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530010000 -0400" stop="20260530014500 -0400"><title>24</title><desc>Chloe is unexpectedly thrust into fieldwork when a woman reports that her boyfriend may be part of the terrorist conspiracy.

Jack and Curtis find their latest efforts to trap Marwan thwarted by the Secret Service, who have orders to arrest Jack for insubordination.

Mike calls on ex-President David Palmer for help as Logan continues to display a lack of leadership.</desc><sub-title>Day 4: 1:00 A.M.-2:00 A.M.</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530013009 -0400" stop="20260530015454 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie goes all out to save a gazebo at a mansion on the historical register from being destroyed, while April gets in trouble with Ron when she accidentally schedules 93 meetings for him on the same day.</desc><sub-title>94 Meetings</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530001907 -0400" stop="20260530014309 -0400"><title>Beavis and Butt-Head Do America</title><desc>Slacker duo Beavis and Butt-Head wake to discover their TV has been stolen. Their search for a new one takes them on a clueless adventure across America, during which they manage to accidentally become America's most wanted.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530063000 +0100" stop="20260530070000 +0100"><title>My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic</title><desc>When Rainbow Dash&#8217;s favorite author, A.K. Yearling, announces her retirement, she convinces Pinkie Pie to go on a quest to find out if the Daring Do book series will be closed forever.</desc><sub-title>Daring Done?</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530011537 -0400" stop="20260530014332 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>In London, artist Bob Osborne takes a laid-back approach to running his B&amp;B, At Home, in Chiswick

On arrival, guests are pleasantly surprised by their first impression of Bob's communal living space-come-mini art gallery, but on closer inspection, the guests are soon dishing the dirt.

Bob's impromptu art class gets mixed reviews and an appraisal from art critic Peter Davies on their efforts leaves some of the guests baffled. But it's at dinner when the guests are really bewildered, as Bob reveals his plans for tomorrow's breakfast.

The next morning, the artist-in-residence is a no show and the DIY breakfast seems to have almost everyone getting into the communal vibe. Unfortunately for Bob, at feedback, his guests' feelings don't make for works of art.</desc><sub-title>At Home</sub-title></programme></tv>