<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260525174500 -0400" stop="20260525183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>A bus accident leaves House with serious head trauma and partial amnesia. He comes to believe that a patient on the bus had a life-threatening disease and struggles to recall who it was, and what they had.</desc><sub-title>House's Head (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260525174024 -0400" stop="20260525180450 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>Jack hopes to be G.E. CEO so he hires a private eye to find any issues about himself. The P.I. exposes Jack's cookie jar collection. Jenna gains weight doing a musical Mystic Pizza, making her beloved by fans but she loses weight, panics.</desc><sub-title>The Collection</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260525161622 -0400" stop="20260525180145 -0400"><title>Frozen</title><desc>Fearless optimist Anna teams up with rugged mountain man Kristoff and his loyal reindeer Sven in an epic journey to find Anna's sister Elsa, whose icy powers have trapped the kingdom of Arendelle in eternal winter.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260525172453 -0400" stop="20260525181132 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>Mike heads out to Poland to bag one of the most exciting and exclusive cars we've ever done - the Lamborghini Uracco. Prices are rising thanks to the company's 50th anniversary and dwindling supply of these 70s supercars. Mike finds a car that's been kept in a collection for years - without turning a wheel. It doesn't start, it can't drive. But it's in great condition in every other way.</desc><sub-title>Lamborghini Urraco</sub-title></programme></tv>