<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522114500 -0400" stop="20260522123000 -0400"><title>Escape to the Country</title><desc>Nicki Chapman is house hunting with a young family who are looking for a new home and a new life in the East Sussex countryside on a healthy &#163;750,000 budget. While in the county, Nicki samples historic Rye's most celebrated seafood.</desc><sub-title>East Sussex</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522114719 -0400" stop="20260522121302 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Joey falls for Phoebe's twin sister, Ursula, making Phoebe feel neglected. Ross has doubts about parenthood when he attends Lamaze classes with Carol and Susan. Meanwhile, Chandler finds himself between a rock and a hard place, when he is told to fire an employee he is attracted to.</desc><sub-title>The One with Two Parts (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522114700 -0400" stop="20260522142449 -0400"><title>Transformers: The Last Knight</title><desc>Having left Earth, Optimus Prime finds his dead home planet, Cybertron, and discovers that he was in fact responsible for its destruction. Optimus learns that he can bring Cybertron back to life, but in order to do so, he will need an artifact that is hidden on Earth.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522170000 +0100" stop="20260522173000 +0100"><title>QI</title><desc>Stephen Fry hosts a festive edition of the quiz show. Alan Davies, Sean Lock, John Sessions and Phill Jupitus attempt to identify the gender of Rudolf the reindeer and guess which Christmas decoration a German village exported worldwide.</desc><sub-title>Advent</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522114713 -0400" stop="20260522121442 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Quirky couple Lynn Self and Ziggy Broome hope to impress with their two-star B&amp;B in Falmouth, Cornwall.

But with two of the guests - Charlotte Church's parents James and Maria Church - already saying that they wouldn't stay anywhere below a four star, it could be an interesting day.

From the offset the guests are very unimpressed by their surroundings - from peeling wallpaper to a dirty toilet brush.

At dinner, when James and Maria reveal the truth about their famous daughter, Nicky reveals she used to be Mr Blobby's fan-mail writer

After an interesting night's sleep, breakfast reduces some of the guests to fits of giggles.</desc><sub-title>Eden Lodge, Falmouth</sub-title></programme></tv>