<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516170000 -0400" stop="20260516174500 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>Monk is hired to clear the name of a famous rap star who is accused of murder.</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk and the Rapper</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516171648 -0400" stop="20260516174345 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>A documentary crew arrives at the offices of Dunder Mifflin to observe the employees and learn about modern management. Manager Michael Scott tries to paint a happy picture, while sales rep Jim fights with his nemesis Dwight and flirts with receptionist Pam.</desc><sub-title>Pilot</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516154940 -0400" stop="20260516174358 -0400"><title>Promare</title><desc>A futuristic firefighting mecha service is created to protect the world.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260516223000 +0100" stop="20260516230000 +0100"><title>Friends</title><desc>Rachel goes on her first date after splitting from Ross... and it's with Mark, her former colleague. Joey is cast in a play and develops a crush on his costar. Monica continues to date Pete, even though she is still not attracted to him.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Tiny T-Shirt</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516170816 -0400" stop="20260516173600 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>B&amp;B newbies Tony Keates and Jeanette Hamer are first to host, at Ye Olde Fighting Cocks in Arnside in Cumbria. Their guests are captivated by the view, but fellow B&amp;Ber Garry Lloyd is less taken by what he thinks is mould on his mattress.

Next to host is Dr Stephen Stanley-Little, owner of Westward Cottage in Hadleigh in Suffolk. While Avril Berry and Alan Fraser are thrilled by its quirky appeal, business-minded couple Tony and Jeannette don't like the standards of cleanliness and decide to roll up their sleeves and take urgent action.

The third hosts are bohemian couple Avril and Alan who own Roulotte Retreat in Melrose, in the Scottish Borders.

The final visit is to The Elgin Hotel in Blackpool where manager Garry LLoyd and owner's daughter Sophie Seddon want to show their 89 room establishment can deliver the personal touch.</desc><sub-title>From Ye Olde Fighting Cocks to The Elgin Hotel</sub-title></programme></tv>