<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260529144500 -0400" stop="20260529151500 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie hits the Pawnee media circuit to promote the Harvest Festival, but Ben freaks out on air when his past is exposed. Meanwhile, April threatens Andy that she'll leave for Indianapolis unless he does her chores.</desc><sub-title>Media Blitz</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260529144157 -0400" stop="20260529150734 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>Carmen's friend is over to study and wants to change out of her dress. When Max hars this, he pulls aposter off his wall to reaveal a hole. He looks through but Carmen sees him and sprays perfume in his eyes. George shrugs it off and tells Max not to do it again. Carmen gets revenge though by taking a picture of Max sleeping with a stuffed animal. This leads Max to bebeaten up at school. While getting stitches, George and Carmen argue and Carmen says George loves Max more. George comes to realize that maybe that is true since he doesn't understand Carmen as well, so he sets off to spend some quality time with her.</desc><sub-title>I Only Have Eyes for You</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260529145750 -0400" stop="20260529171440 -0400"><title>Jurassic World: Rebirth</title><desc>Five years post-Jurassic World: Dominion (2022), an expedition braves isolated equatorial regions to extract DNA from three massive prehistoric creatures for a groundbreaking medical breakthrough.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260529200500 +0100" stop="20260529210000 +0100"><title>An Idiot Abroad</title><desc>Karl is sent to Rio de Janeiro, Brazil to see the iconic Christ the Redeemer statue. However, he finds himself increasingly infuriated by the intense heat and Ricky and Steve's attempts to have him interact with the noisy locals.</desc><sub-title>Brazil</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260529144618 -0400" stop="20260529151144 -0400"><title>Mind Field</title><desc>We may value having Freedom of Choice, but are we actually happier when we have limited choices...or even no choice at all? Do we truly have control over our decisions, or are they really predetermined by other forces? My fellow YouTubers and I have our minds read by a &#8220;box&#8221; that reveals who - or what - is really calling the shots.</desc><sub-title>Freedom of Choice</sub-title></programme></tv>