<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531161500 -0400" stop="20260531170000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>A painter's undiagnosed illness affects his work, and House and his team must look at the man's paintings to determine what's wrong with him.</desc><sub-title>Adverse Events</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531161725 -0400" stop="20260531182623 -0400"><title>Ted 2</title><desc>Newlywed couple Ted and Tami-Lynn want to have a baby, but in order to qualify to be a parent, Ted will have to prove he's a person in a court of law.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531160642 -0400" stop="20260531175051 -0400"><title>The Garfield Movie</title><desc>Garfield (voiced by Chris Pratt), the world-famous, Monday-hating, lasagna-loving indoor cat, is about to have a wild outdoor adventure. After an unexpected reunion with his long-lost father - scruffy street cat Vic (voiced by Samuel L. Jackson) - Garfield and his canine friend Odie are forced from their perfectly pampered life into joining Vic in a hilarious, high-stakes heist.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531210000 +0100" stop="20260531220000 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>Trainee doctor Martha Jones has her hands full balancing her medical studies with placating her demanding family. So the last thing she needs is to find that the hospital where she works has been transported to the moon, where it's invaded by an overbearing alien police force. There she encounters a patient called John Smith, who seems curiously at ease with the situation&#8230;</desc><sub-title>Smith and Jones</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531163500 -0400" stop="20260531170233 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>At the Abbey House in Penrith, Cumbria, Ian and Samantha Sugden pride themselves on their simple but scrupulously clean rooms.

The rivals then travel to Compton House in Newark, Nottinghamshire, where sisters Lisa Holloway and Becky Waltman offer antique filled rooms and five star breakfasts.

The third visit is to the White Horse Inn in Ripon, Yorkshire managed by Dave and Jo Bate. Their basic rooms, and pub breakfasts don't impress though.

Last is the Old Farmhouse, Chester, run by retired teachers Ed and Jane Mitchell.</desc><sub-title>From Abbey House to the Old Farmhouse</sub-title></programme></tv>