<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530141300 -0400" stop="20260530161500 -0400"><title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title><desc>After stealing a mysterious orb in the far reaches of outer space, Peter Quill from Earth is now the main target of a manhunt led by the villain known as Ronan the Accuser. To help fight Ronan and his team and save the galaxy from his power, Quill creates a team of space heroes known as the "Guardians of the Galaxy" to save the galaxy.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530143908 -0400" stop="20260530150522 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Joey buys a big screen TV and two leather recliners with his newfound money. Monica has a catering job for one of her parents' friends and becomes infatuated. Ross and Rachel attempt to have their first real date, but Rachel laughs every time they kiss. When they try again the next evening, they are interrupted when Ross is called into the museum.</desc><sub-title>The One Where Ross and Rachel... You Know</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530143559 -0400" stop="20260530164832 -0400"><title>Superman</title><desc>Superman must reconcile his alien Kryptonian heritage with his human upbringing as reporter Clark Kent. As the embodiment of truth, justice and the American way he soon finds himself in a world that views these as old-fashioned.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530190000 +0100" stop="20260530200500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>Richard races the new Mazda MX5, worth &#163;18,000 against a greyhound worth &#163;25,000. Jeremy compares driving a Honda NSX around Laguna Seca in a video game to the real thing. The Austin Healy Sprite and modified Peugot 306 go head-to-head on the Prescott Hill Climb course to see which is best and there's the Top Gear Awards, where James is awarded the Golden Cock. David Walliams is the Star in a Reasonably Priced Car.</desc><sub-title>Mazda MX-5 vs. Greyhound</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530142435 -0400" stop="20260530144937 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Whether you're a skeptic or a believer in the supernatural, you have to admit there are things out there your brain just can't quite explain. Get ready for a series of games and experiments designed to test your brain's sixth sense. If you play along, you'll discover that your brain actually knows more about the unknown than you might think.</desc><sub-title>Paranormal</sub-title></programme></tv>