<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260519193000 -0400" stop="20260519200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Louise must face her fear of public pooping when her class goes on an overnight trip to the aquarium. Meanwhile, Linda enlists the family to make a video for her parents' anniversary.</desc><sub-title>Poops!... I Didn't Do It Again</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260519192412 -0400" stop="20260519194849 -0400"><title>New Girl</title><desc>When Schmidt's plans for his 29th birthday fall apart, Jess takes charge and enlists the help of her school's party hungry vice-principal. Meanwhile, Nick begrudgingly has his first date at Schmidt's party with a beautiful lawyer who harbors a secret, and the gang wonders who placed a 50 dollar bill in the douchebag jar.</desc><sub-title>The Story of the 50</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260519184214 -0400" stop="20260519202105 -0400"><title>Evangelion: 3.0 You Can (Not) Redo</title><desc>14 years have passed since the near third impact. Most of the world has changed except Shinji Ikari who awakens, unaged in a new and strange environment. Misato has formed a group that is separate from Nerv. The fight is far from over but the biggest struggle might be against humans and former allies.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520003000 +0100" stop="20260520010000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>Failing to topple Megatron, an exiled Starscream plans his revenge. He uses World War II era machines and five personality components to create the Combaticons, which prove very powerful in their Bruticus form.</desc><sub-title>Starscream's Brigade</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260519192519 -0400" stop="20260519195223 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The competition starts at Lilly's Pad in Lincolnshire, where Sue and Louise aim to win over their guests with their personalities, but there are mixed reactions to the themed teddy bears.</desc><sub-title>Lilly's Pad</sub-title></programme></tv>