<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260525193000 -0400" stop="20260525200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>When Tina is forced to listen to Spanish audio lessons in the library to improve her grade, she develops an unexpected crush. Meanwhile, Louise and Gene want to dunk Mr. Frond at the Wagstaff Spring Fair.</desc><sub-title>Y Tu Tina Tambi&#233;n</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260525194329 -0400" stop="20260525200723 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>When Michael visits Dunder Mifflin corporate headquarters in New York on Valentine's Day, he and Jan are both in for a surprise. Meanwhile, back in Scranton, the office staff celebrates Valentine's Day grade school style.</desc><sub-title>Valentine's Day</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260525180145 -0400" stop="20260525195302 -0400"><title>Deadpool</title><desc>This is the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter ego Deadpool. Armed with his new abilities and a dark, twisted sense of humor, Deadpool hunts down the man who nearly destroyed his life.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260525190339 -0400" stop="20260525195619 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>The team test holiday-related myths while counting down the top 10 myths as voted by the viewers. A frozen turkey can explode if dropped into deep fryer too fast. If you put a silver spoon in a bottle of champagne, the bubbles will last longer. A falling icicle can kill a person. A clothed snowman melts faster than a naked one. A stream of urine can freeze in freezing temperatures. Lighting the fireplace makes the rest of the house colder.</desc><sub-title>Viewers-Choice/Christmas Special</sub-title></programme></tv>