<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523170000 -0400" stop="20260523174500 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>When Monk suffers from insomnia, he ventures into the night and stumbles upon a murder.</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk Is Up All Night</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523171856 -0400" stop="20260523174134 -0400"><title>Everybody Hates Chris</title><desc>Toyna keeps getting Chris into trouble and Chris is sick of it, so he decides to hang out at Greg's house without permission from either of their parents. When Greg's father comes home and Chris finds out Greg isn't allowed to have anyone over when his dad's not home, Chris hides in the closet to avoid getting into trouble.</desc><sub-title>Everybody Hates Greg</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523164257 -0400" stop="20260523184506 -0400"><title>1917</title><desc>April 6th, 1917. As an infantry battalion assembles to wage war deep in enemy territory, two soldiers are assigned to race against time and deliver a message that will stop 1,600 men from walking straight into a deadly trap.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523220000 +0100" stop="20260523223000 +0100"><title>Friends</title><desc>Chandler agrees to spend Thanksgiving in a shipping crate as penance for kissing Kathy. The gang decides to give each other Secret Santa gifts. After Monica gets ice in her eye, she ends up visiting Richard's son, who is as attracted to Monica as his father was.</desc><sub-title>The One with Chandler in a Box</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523171306 -0400" stop="20260523180600 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Can firing a bullet into the shell of an aircraft cause explosive decompression? Can a loaded .22-caliber gun cartridge be used as a replacement fuse in a car's ignition? Can a car be ripped off its rear axle?</desc><sub-title>Explosive Decompression</sub-title></programme></tv>