<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518200000 -0400" stop="20260518210000 -0400"><title>Salvage Hunters</title><desc>Drew Pritchard continues his search for valuable scrap items in the UK, visiting an antique dealer whose stock includes a lamp that could make his entire trip worthwhile. He also searches for treasures in a Somerset estate's coach house</desc><sub-title>Episode 3</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518185258 -0400" stop="20260518205439 -0400"><title>Bad Boys</title><desc>Marcus Burnett is a henpecked family man. Mike Lowrey is a footloose and fancy free ladies' man. Both Miami policemen, they have 72 hours to reclaim a consignment of drugs stolen from under their station's nose. To complicate matters, in order to get the assistance of the sole witness to a murder, they have to pretend to be each other.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260518185629 -0400" stop="20260518203942 -0400"><title>Toy Story 4</title><desc>Woody, Buzz Lightyear and the rest of the gang embark on a road trip with Bonnie and a new toy named Forky. The adventurous journey turns into an unexpected reunion as Woody's slight detour leads him to his long-lost friend Bo Peep. As Woody and Bo discuss the old days, they soon start to realize that they're two worlds apart when it comes to what they want from life as a toy.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260519010000 +0100" stop="20260519013000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>A fleeing Shir&#333; is eventually cornered by Rin, who offers to spare his life if he gives her his Command Seals. However, he refuses, prompting Rin to try and kill him. Both are then distracted by a scream downstairs and he and Rin find an unconscious girl. As Rin attempts to heal her, a dagger flies through an open door, aimed for Rin, but Shir&#333; blocks it with his arm, wounding himself in the process. He runs outside to find the female Servant, which is of the Rider class, and repels an attack by her. Shir&#333; considers summoning Saber via Command Seal, but decides it is too risky to get her involved and resolves to confront Rider himself. Rider resumes her assault, and Shir&#333; is nearly killed by her until Rin rescues him. At Rin's home, Shir&#333; and Rin decide to form a temporary truce to find Rider's Master.</desc><sub-title>Two Magi (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518200228 -0400" stop="20260518202704 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 17</sub-title></programme></tv>