<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524144500 -0400" stop="20260524151500 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>Leslie goes on a crusade to improve park safety after Jerry is mugged, which is later discovered to be a lie. Meanwhile, Ron tries to teach the office self-defense, but winds up injuring Andy instead.</desc><sub-title>Park Safety</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524144604 -0400" stop="20260524151053 -0400"><title>The Big Bang Theory</title><desc>Sheldon's solution to Penny's financial difficulty leads to a confrontation between Leonard and Penny's ex-boyfriend.</desc><sub-title>The Financial Permeability</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524141028 -0400" stop="20260524164806 -0400"><title>Pulp Fiction</title><desc>A burger-loving hit man, his philosophical partner, a drug-addled gangster's moll and a washed-up boxer converge in this sprawling, comedic crime caper. Their adventures unfurl in three stories that ingeniously trip back and forth in time.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524190000 +0100" stop="20260524200500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>Richard takes part in the Pamplona Bull Run and drives the Lamborghini Murci&#233;lago Roadster. Jeremy drives the Ford F150 Lightning pick-up truck, which is inexplicably the world's best-selling car and describes it as the worst car he had ever driven.James put his degree in music to fine use by trying to re-create the Top Gear theme tune using car engines.Richard tries a bit of drifting in the Monaro with the D1 drifting team.</desc><sub-title>Hammond Runs With the Bulls</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524144513 -0400" stop="20260524150903 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Gut Strings, Absinthe, Belt Buckles, and Lever Locks and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Gut Strings, Absinthe, Belt Buckles, Lever Locks</sub-title></programme></tv>