<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518190000 -0400" stop="20260518193000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Bob and the kids help a down-on-his-luck restaurant owner, while Linda and Teddy get carried away with St. Patrick's Day festivities.</desc><sub-title>Flat-Top O' the Morning to Ya</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518185325 -0400" stop="20260518191828 -0400"><title>How I Met Your Mother</title><desc>Barney takes Ted to matchmaker Ellen Pierce, but while Barney gets thrown out, Ellen promises to find a woman for Ted within three days. This promise has disastrous results: the woman that suits him the best has already a boyfriend. Lily and Marshall have problems with some sort of cockroach or mouse that is in the apartment and they cannot get rid of.</desc><sub-title>Matchmaker</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260518185629 -0400" stop="20260518203942 -0400"><title>Toy Story 4</title><desc>Woody, Buzz Lightyear and the rest of the gang embark on a road trip with Bonnie and a new toy named Forky. The adventurous journey turns into an unexpected reunion as Woody's slight detour leads him to his long-lost friend Bo Peep. As Woody and Bo discuss the old days, they soon start to realize that they're two worlds apart when it comes to what they want from life as a toy.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260519000000 +0100" stop="20260519003000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>Megatron causes his fellow Decepticons to be infected with the deadly Cosmic Rust. Perceptor is captured to find a cure and he does, learning that element X will do the job. The Decepticons are cured, but then they use Perceptor to spread the Cosmic Rust to the Autobots and element X is in short supply.</desc><sub-title>Cosmic Rust</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518183907 -0400" stop="20260518190604 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The third visit of the week is to Roseheart Kingdom, B&amp;B, retreat and therapy centre run by Jacqueline and Tim Bucknell in Shropshire, where animals are very much the VIPs.</desc><sub-title>Roseheart Kingdom</sub-title></programme></tv>