<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524032000 -0400" stop="20260524034500 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Phoebe is rushed to the hospital for the birth of her brother's triplets. While there, Joey winds up with severe sympathy pains that turn out to be kidney stones. Meanwhile, Rachel tries to set Monica up on a date with a male nurse.</desc><sub-title>The One Hundredth</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524032348 -0400" stop="20260524034815 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>Michael, being Michael Scott, overreacts to an 'injury' he has. This steers everyone away from realising that Dwight is the one with a more serious injury. No matter how ill or injured you are though, if you call shotgun, you get the front seat, no matter what...at least according to Michael.</desc><sub-title>The Injury</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524030449 -0400" stop="20260524050305 -0400"><title>28 Years Later</title><desc>A group of survivors of the rage virus live on a small island. When one of the group leaves the island on a mission into the mainland, he discovers secrets, wonders, and horrors that have mutated not only the infected but other survivors.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524083000 +0100" stop="20260524090000 +0100"><title>The Simpsons</title><desc>Grampa begins dating Bea Simmons, another resident of the Springfield Retirement Castle, but she dies. She was a very rich woman, and leaves all her money to Grampa. He is at first unsure how to spend it, and invites suggestions from all-comers who, apart from Lisa, are greedy and want it for themselves. He ultimately donates it to make much needed improvements to the retirement home, telling everybody: "Dignity's on me, friends."</desc><sub-title>Old Money</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524031805 -0400" stop="20260524041044 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>In this episode of MythBusters, Jamie and Adam explore a titanic sized legend. Will a sinking ship suck you down as it goes under? Bored goldfish or just plain stupid? We'll find out if goldfish can remember anything for longer than 3 seconds. A musical myth with highly explosive results, will putting a lit firecracker down the neck of trombone make your music any sweeter? The MythBusters don't just tell the myths, they put them to the test.</desc><sub-title>Sinking Titanic</sub-title></programme></tv>