<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517131500 -0400" stop="20260517134500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>To track down the infamous arms dealer Dan "Daniel" Valdano, Jake and Terry go undercover at an illegal gambling club, but when Holt gets involved to coach the two in the art of poker, his addiction resurfaces. Meanwhile, Boyle buys a food truck that was formerly used in a brutal string of murders without telling his investor, Amy, and Hitchcock and Scully challenge Rosa to a "Butt-lympics".</desc><sub-title>Bad Beat</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517130914 -0400" stop="20260517133413 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>When Michael is forced to pick a low-grade health care plan for his employees, he tells Dwight to do it for him. When Dwight chooses an extraordinarily bad plan for the Scranton Branch, the workers complain and Michael hides in his office, not wanting to face the wrath of his employees.</desc><sub-title>Health Care</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517111930 -0400" stop="20260517133838 -0400"><title>The Fate of the Furious</title><desc>When a mysterious woman seduces Dominic Toretto into the world of terrorism and a betrayal of those closest to him, the crew face trials that will test them as never before.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517180000 +0100" stop="20260517184500 +0100"><title>House</title><desc>A woman comes down with symptoms of African sleeping sickness, but there seems to be no way she could have contracted it. House and his aides must ask a few tough questions and make some tough decisions in order to try to save her.</desc><sub-title>Fidelity</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517124940 -0400" stop="20260517131753 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>In Whaley Bridge, Derbyshire, Springbank Guest House owner Susan Torkington offers her guests the chance to learn cheerleading. But the blowback from a trio of stray hairs leaves her fuming.</desc><sub-title>Springbank Guest House</sub-title></programme></tv>