<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260519073000 -0400" stop="20260519080000 -0400"><title>The King of Queens</title><desc>Doug has to deliver to a man who always answers his door in nothing but a very little towel. Arthur decides where he is getting buried and has one plot for himself and one for another, so he is trying to find someone to be buried by. Holly asks Carrie to help her walk the countless dogs she has to walks, but Carrie doesn't know what she is getting herself into.</desc><sub-title>Multiple Plots</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260519072750 -0400" stop="20260519075259 -0400"><title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title><desc>When the gang learns that they are in danger of losing their bar due to a zoning mishap, they resort to some outlandish and extreme methods to prevent that from happening. Meanwhile, Frank isn&#8217;t too happy when his wife returns to town.</desc><sub-title>The Gang Goes Jihad</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260519061832 -0400" stop="20260519074807 -0400"><title>My Neighbor Totoro</title><desc>Two sisters move to the country with their father in order to be closer to their hospitalized mother, and discover the surrounding trees are inhabited by Totoros, magical spirits of the forest. When the youngest runs away from home, the older sister seeks help from the spirits to find her.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260519123000 +0100" stop="20260519133000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>The venue for the first programme is La Lanterna in Letchworth, Hertfordshire. Twenty-eight-year-old owner and head chef Alex offers modern Italian cuisine, a taste of Little Italy in England's first garden city, and the restaurant is run by his best mate, maitre d' Gavin, helped by Alex's ex-air hostess girlfriend Emily.

Alex has no customers, cookers that don't work and an expensive menu that's about as authentically Italian as a Hawaiian Pizza. He re-mortgaged his house to buy the business, it's losing &#163;1,000 a week, he hasn't slept for months but still runs round town in a flash car (number plate: A1CHEF) that's worth more than the restaurant. Running out of money, inspiration and energy, Alex is on the verge of losing EVERYTHING.

It's a prime restaurant for a dose of TOUGH LOVE - Ramsay-style. But can a strict diet of brutal honesty, radical food surgery and undiluted energy turn things round, or is it only a matter of time before the lights go out at La Lanterna for good?</desc><sub-title>La Lanterna</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260519071505 -0400" stop="20260519073910 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 15</sub-title></programme></tv>