<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522170000 -0400" stop="20260522174500 -0400"><title>Bones</title><desc>The team is on the case when human remains are found inside a barrel of wine during a wine tasting. When the victim turns out to be a wine critic whose scathing reviews were capable of sending a vineyard to its ruin, everyone from the winery's owner to the victim's own wife becomes a suspect.</desc><sub-title>The Critic in the Cabernet</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522154040 -0400" stop="20260522181105 -0400"><title>Bad Boys II</title><desc>Miami is being flooded with ecstasy that's coming from Cuba through drug lord Johnny Tapia. Detectives Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett are on the case, and are determined to bring the man to justice. Additional drama is provided by friction with the DEA, which counts Marcus' younger sister Sydney among its agents, and from Marcus possibly transferring out of the department, leaving Mike without his longtime partner.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522160026 -0400" stop="20260522173745 -0400"><title>Tenacious D in the Pick of Destiny</title><desc>To become the greatest band of all time, two slackers, wannabe-rockers set out on a quest to steal a legendary guitar pick that gives its holders incredible guitar skills, from a maximum security Rock and Roll museum.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522220000 +0100" stop="20260522223000 +0100"><title>Friends</title><desc>Ross's new girlfriend seems nearly perfect until he visits her house and discovers that her apartment is incredibly dirty.  Chandler helps Joey pick out a thoughtful present for Kathy's birthday. Rachel attempts to finish a crossword puzzle by herself. And Phoebe helps Monica cater a funeral.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Dirty Girl</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522163526 -0400" stop="20260522170409 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>First to host this time is Mrs Tee in the New Forest

Mrs Tee's eccentric ways charm the guests on arrival. But not everyone's room is up to scratch. John and Neil's bathroom window needs fixing and Alistair and Emma Mundell find they are sharing their room with ladybirds, cobwebs and dust.

Mrs Tee's group activity is a master class in mushrooms master class and her home-cooked dinner also consists of mushrooms.

At check out time while most of the guests agree that Mrs Tee's rooms just aren't up to standard, Alistair and Emma are the toughest critics.</desc><sub-title>Gorse Meadow,  New Forest</sub-title></programme></tv>