<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524010000 -0400" stop="20260524014500 -0400"><title>24</title><desc>Jack and Paul enlist civilian help when they must fight off soldiers sent to kill them by McLennan-Forster.

Tensions flair between Tony and Michelle as she assumes command of CTU. Sarah tests Michelle's authority by giving her an ultimatum.

Audrey reevaluates her feelings for Jack, while Marwan sets the next phase of his plan in motion.</desc><sub-title>Day 4: 7:00 P.M.-8:00 P.M.</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524010925 -0400" stop="20260524013339 -0400"><title>Impractical Jokers</title><desc>Joe, Murr, Q, and Sal bring you their favorite moments from season one. The guys discuss their most shocking incidents, the best reactions, and reveal never before seen moments from the cutting room floor.</desc><sub-title>The Stoop Sessions Part 2</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523231357 -0400" stop="20260524013332 -0400"><title>The Running Man</title><desc>A desperate contestant enters a globally broadcast death game where hired killers track participants across international borders. Cameras document every chase, every near miss, every kill. Audiences vote, sponsors intervene, and survival becomes performance art. The hunted runs while the world watches, entertains itself, and waits for the inevitable collapse of flesh against choreography.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524060000 +0100" stop="20260524063000 +0100"><title>My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic</title><desc>Applejack and her siblings discover a few surprises when they set out to unravel the mystery of the feud between the Apple and Pear families.</desc><sub-title>The Perfect Pear</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524011022 -0400" stop="20260524015709 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>The Boxster is the car that saved Porsche from going out of business when recession hit in the 90s. It may have been called the poor man&#8217;s Porsche, but this was unfair - it was 80% Porsche 911, for half the price. Although that &#8216;half price&#8217; was still more than most could afford, until Mike tracks down an example with a bargain basement price tag.</desc><sub-title>Porsche Boxster 3.2S</sub-title></programme></tv>