<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523025500 -0400" stop="20260523032000 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Joey convinces Ross to pick him as his best man instead of Chandler. He throws a great bachelor party, but the next morning he's shocked to find out that the wedding ring is missing and he suspects that the stripper stole it. Meanwhile, Phoebe is experiencing major mood swings due to her pregnancy and the girls decide to throw her a baby shower to cheer her up, but it only makes matters worse.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Worst Best Man Ever</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523023716 -0400" stop="20260523042952 -0400"><title>School of Rock</title><desc>Fired from his band and hard up for cash, guitarist and vocalist Dewey Finn finagles his way into a job as a fifth-grade substitute teacher at a private school, where he secretly begins teaching his straight-A students the finer points of rock 'n' roll and the power of sticking it to the man. But as the school&#8217;s stern principal closes in and the Battle of the Bands looms, Dewey risks everything to prove that rock 'n' roll can change lives.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523024535 -0400" stop="20260523043349 -0400"><title>Edward Scissorhands</title><desc>In a castle high on top of a hill lives an inventor's greatest creation - Edward, a near-complete person. The creator died before he could finish Edward's hands; instead, he is left with metal scissors for hands. Since then, he has lived alone, until a kind lady called Peg discovers him and welcomes him into her home. At first, everyone welcomes him into the community, but soon things begin to take a change for the worse.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523080000 +0100" stop="20260523083000 +0100"><title>The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title><desc>War breaks out when the girl Will likes plants a big one on Carlton.</desc><sub-title>Grumpy Young Men</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523030646 -0400" stop="20260523033150 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Replica Clay Pipes, Drinking Fountains, Orange Liqueur, and Compound Bows and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Replica Clay Pipes, Drinking Fountains, Orange Liqueur, Compound Bows</sub-title></programme></tv>