<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517080000 -0400" stop="20260517083000 -0400"><title>The Nanny</title><desc>Fran goes to her former fianc&#233; Danny's funeral, and fearing she may end up alone, she pushes Maxwell for a commitment.</desc><sub-title>Danny's Dead and Who's Got the Will?</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517075611 -0400" stop="20260517082231 -0400"><title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title><desc>After discovering that he might have cancer, Mac and Dennis attempt to find a woman who will sleep with Charlie.  In the midst of their search, Mac falls in love with a transsexual he meets at the bar named Carmen.  Overwhelmed by the extra workload that she had to take on since Charlie has taken a leave of absence, Dee tries to get Dennis to hire a recently out of work actress friend to help out.</desc><sub-title>Charlie Has Cancer</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517074030 -0400" stop="20260517093315 -0400"><title>Top Gun</title><desc>The Top Gun Naval Fighter Weapons School is where the best of the best train to refine their elite flying skills. When hotshot fighter pilot Maverick is sent to the school, his reckless attitude and cocky demeanor put him at odds with the other pilots, especially the cool and collected Iceman.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517130000 +0100" stop="20260517133000 +0100"><title>Lucky Star</title><desc>Konata's cousin Yutaka Kobayakawa, who is also Konata's cousin Yui's little sister, has passed her high school entrance exams and will be living with Konata and her father from now on.

Before a sick Yutaka took her exams, she met a girl who gave her a handkerchief.  On the day of orientation and uniform fitting at Yutaka's new high school, she meets the girl who gave her the handkerchief and gives it back to her.  They become friends and part ways.  It was then that Yutaka realizes that she never asked for the girl's name.

Kagami and Tsukasa come over the Konata's house and become acquainted with Yutaka.

This week on Lucky Channel, Akira feels gypped by the fact that she only had one line in the actual show, but she wasn't on-screen.  So, she decideds to initiate "Project Full Appearance in Actual Show!!!" and tells the audience to send in their support to get her in the actual show.</desc><sub-title>Under One Roof</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517080306 -0400" stop="20260517083046 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>In Sunbury on Thames owner Simon Bailey and French manager Pierre Cudon offer a stylish stay with a certain je ne sais quoi. The guests follow in Henry VIII's footsteps with a game of real tennis at Hampton Court Palace. Over dinner, Jo leaves the other B&amp;Bers speechless when she reveals the lengths she will go to for her hotel.</desc><sub-title>From Nateby Inn to Ammonite Lodge</sub-title></programme></tv>