<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520003000 -0400" stop="20260520010000 -0400"><title>Two and a Half Men</title><desc>Just released after long mental therapy in a strict "stress clinic", Alan's life quickly turns nightmarish again: On the ride home, he learns that Jake sired Megan's baby and Walden took his place as Lyndsey's lover and packed his bags. When Evelyn pretends she isn't home, Alan must spend the night in the storage Walden arranged for his possessions. Then the cards are reshuffled again.</desc><sub-title>Frodo's Headshots</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520002757 -0400" stop="20260520005234 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>While Michael and Dwight are out of the office for the day trying to close a deal on a new condo for Michael, Jim and Pam arrange for the staff to participate in an "Office Olympics," where the workers play strange, invented games (among them, Dunderball, Hate Ball...and Pam Pong) that they usually play while the boss is out.  At the end of the day, the festivities cheer up everyone - even the oblivious Michael.</desc><sub-title>Office Olympics</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260520003858 -0400" stop="20260520021454 -0400"><title>Shrek the Third</title><desc>Reluctantly designated as the heir to the land of Far, Far Away, Shrek hatches a plan to install the rebellious Artie as the new king while Princess Fiona tries to fend off a coup d'&#233;tat by the jilted Prince Charming.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520053000 +0100" stop="20260520060000 +0100"><title>..programmes start at 6.00am</title><desc /><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520002051 -0400" stop="20260520011501 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Gordon takes on an ex-boxer and his feisty wife whose barroom brawls are scaring away customers 

Gordon might be famed for his aggression in the kitchen but he meets his match this week as Kitchen Nightmares heads to rural Wales

The Fish &amp; Anchor restaurant and bar near Lampeter is run by a couple of bruisers, ex-boxer Mike and his mouthy wife Caron.

A self taught cook, Mike is a one-man pressure cooker in the kitchen as he struggles to cope with a menu too vast and wide ranging for his skills.

While Mike gets steamed up in the kitchen, Carol's getting hot under the collar in the restaurant. Her unique front-of-house management style includes abusing the customers and her husband in equal measure. Every night they go twelve rounds with the local clientele who are fast deserting them to the tune of a &#163;1,000 per week loss.

Enter Gordon, who finds himself cast as marriage counsellor in a culinary battlefield. It&#8217;s a last-ditch attempt to reverse the restaurant&#8217;s disastrous reputation and put some love back into the kitchen as well as on plates. Will Mike take on board a last-minute reality check in the fight of his life, or stay on the ropes and sink?</desc><sub-title>The Fish &amp; Anchor</sub-title></programme></tv>