<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521193000 -0400" stop="20260521200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>The kids meet a mysterious old woman at a hotel on Halloween as Louise plots her revenge for a candy transgression; Bob and Linda donate blood at a vampire-themed blood mobile.</desc><sub-title>Heartbreak Hotel-oween</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521190057 -0400" stop="20260521203128 -0400"><title>Johnny English</title><desc>A lowly pencil pusher working for MI7, Johnny English is suddenly promoted to super spy after Agent One is assassinated and every other agent is blown up at his funeral. When a billionaire entrepreneur sponsors the exhibition of the Crown Jewels&#8212;and the valuable gems disappear on the opening night and on English's watch&#8212;the newly-designated agent must jump into action to find the thief and recover the missing gems.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521181517 -0400" stop="20260521201346 -0400"><title>Raiders of the Lost Ark</title><desc>When Dr. Indiana Jones &#8211; the tweed-suited professor who just happens to be a celebrated archaeologist &#8211; is hired by the government to locate the legendary Ark of the Covenant, he finds himself up against the entire Nazi regime.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522003000 +0100" stop="20260522010000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 52</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521192256 -0400" stop="20260521201549 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>In the first hour of Ramsay's Great British Nightmare special Gordon visits The Dovecote where Mick is a former trucker and burger van operator who has opened a bistro with his wife and adopted daughter, Michelle. Mick, however, has very little cooking ability, using orange squash to make a sauce and microwaving unrefrigerated, vacuum-sealed pre-cooked lamb shanks. Mick is adamant that the problems in the kitchen are not his fault and his stubbornness causes a rift with his wife and daughter. Gordon takes the business matters out of Mick's hands, kicking him out of the kitchen. His daughter, Michelle, is placed in charge of the kitchen. She rises to the challenge and while Mick is not convinced over replacing his microwave food, the reopening is a success. Months later, the restaurant is making profit. Ramsay sends Michelle for further culinary training and she impresses him with freshly cooked food. The restaurant was renamed Martins' Bistro during production.</desc><sub-title>The Dovecote</sub-title></programme></tv>