<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260526134500 -0400" stop="20260526141500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Holt and Jake become suspicious of a new Nine-Nine employee. Amy goes full-on Marie Kondo to declutter the bullpen.</desc><sub-title>The Honeypot</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260526121612 -0400" stop="20260526142011 -0400"><title>Hot Fuzz</title><desc>Former London constable Nicholas Angel finds it difficult to adapt to his new assignment in the sleepy British village of Sandford. Not only does he miss the excitement of the big city, but he also has a well-meaning oaf for a partner. However, when a series of grisly accidents rocks Sandford, Angel smells something rotten in the idyllic village.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260526124131 -0400" stop="20260526142608 -0400"><title>The Lego Ninjago Movie</title><desc>Six young ninjas Lloyd, Jay, Kai, Cole, Zane and Nya are tasked with defending their island home, called Ninjago. By night, they're gifted warriors, using their skills and awesome fleet of vehicles to fight villains and monsters. By day, they're ordinary teens struggling against their greatest enemy: high school.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260526140137 -0400" stop="20260526142541 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Customized Knee Replacements, Leaf Springs, Lavender, and Rivets and Rivet Tools and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Customized Knee Replacements, Leaf Springs, Lavender Essential Oil, Rivets and Rivet Tools</sub-title></programme></tv>