<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523100000 -0400" stop="20260523103000 -0400"><title>Frasier</title><desc>A lifetime achievement award sends Frasier into an existential crisis which culminates in a battle of wits with his old mentor; Daphne's weight gain doesn't go unnoticed.</desc><sub-title>Frasier's Edge</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523101134 -0400" stop="20260523103551 -0400"><title>The Middle</title><desc>Frankie fears for her job when a motivational consultant comes to get the sale team into shape. While Frankie is putting in many extra hours, Mike has to deal with the children and their issues, including making the house more fun for Axl and his friends, giving advice to Sue's ex-boyfriend and helping Brick with a school project.</desc><sub-title>The Fun House</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523093713 -0400" stop="20260523111233 -0400"><title>Kung Fu Panda</title><desc>To everyone's surprise, including his own, Po, an overweight, clumsy panda, is chosen as protector of the Valley of Peace. His suitability will soon be tested as the valley's arch-enemy is on his way.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523150000 +0100" stop="20260523160000 +0100"><title>The Chase (2009)</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 127</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523094656 -0400" stop="20260523101420 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>It's Dave 'Butterfly' Botha's turn to host, at his two-star establishment on the Isle of Wight. Tension builds from the outset as Wayne and Deborah discover that they'll be spending the night in one of the tepees in the garden... with an outdoor toilet.

Dave's ace in the hole is paragliding lessons, which brings the group back together through the art of flight. Dave opts for a BBQ dinner - despite the freezing weather. After a restless night's sleep in their tepee Wayne and Deborah claim they have been served watery eggs and rubbery sausages for breakfast. How will the ever-positive host take the criticism?</desc><sub-title>Butterfly Paragliding B&amp;B, Isle of Wight</sub-title></programme></tv>