<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531193000 -0400" stop="20260531200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Bob and Linda accept a Valentine's Day dinner invitation from the chef of a fancy restaurant; the kids have a scheme to get cheap Valentine's Day candy, but first they'll have to make it past an unusually strict babysitter.</desc><sub-title>Ferry on My Wayward Bob and Linda</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531191457 -0400" stop="20260531194902 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>The Scranton branch was getting ready for their new employees to arrive in from the defunct Stamford branch. Pam was especially excited to be reunited with Jim. While, Michael was most concerned with impressing his new staff.</desc><sub-title>The Merger</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531192826 -0400" stop="20260531212923 -0400"><title>Tetris</title><desc>An enterprising game developer risks everything in a race to outmaneuver duplicitous insiders to negotiate a deal with Soviet Union bureaucrats for the international licensing rights to what would eventually become one of the most recognizable and widely played games in history.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260601003000 +0100" stop="20260601010000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>Astrotrain tricks a race living on one of Saturn's moons, Titan, into thinking he is a god and gets them to do his bidding, which includes getting a hold of a newly discovered power.</desc><sub-title>The God Gambit</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531193930 -0400" stop="20260531200700 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>In Whaley Bridge, Derbyshire, Springbank Guest House owner Susan Torkington offers her guests the chance to learn cheerleading. But the blowback from a trio of stray hairs leaves her fuming.</desc><sub-title>Springbank Guest House</sub-title></programme></tv>