<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517141500 -0400" stop="20260517144500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>On Thanksgiving, alcohol provides a temporary fix to Jake and Amy's parental problems, and a pilfered pie awakens the ruthless interrogator in Holt.</desc><sub-title>Two Turkeys</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517135828 -0400" stop="20260517142333 -0400"><title>How I Met Your Mother</title><desc>Ted's outlook on his continuing search for love is altered when he rediscovers a shirt that has not seen daylight in years. Meanwhile, Barney amuses himself by coaxing Robin into sacrificing her job by saying completely outlandish things on air live for a cash reward.</desc><sub-title>Return of the Shirt</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517133838 -0400" stop="20260517153428 -0400"><title>Baby Driver</title><desc>Coerced into working for a crime boss, a young getaway driver must face the music when a doomed heist threatens his life, love, and freedom.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517190000 +0100" stop="20260517201500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>The lads hand over testing duties to their mothers to review a range of new small cars:. They test the Renault Modus, Honda Jazz and Peugeot 1007. Jeremy drives the Cadillac CTS-V and didn't like it that much. Richard tests 'Mondeo man's' new favourite car, the new BMW 3 Series. The Star in a Reasonably Priced Car is Omid Djalili.</desc><sub-title>The Boys' Mother's Review Cars</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517134233 -0400" stop="20260517142920 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>Mike takes the ultimate plunge and invests in a car - and a boat, all in one. It&#8217;s the Amphicar, an amphibious vehicle that Edd has been dreaming of for years. But when he peels back the layers and discovers the car&#8217;s problems are serious, will he find himself in deep water and rinse away all the profit? This challenge truly puts Mike and Edd&#8217;s skills to the test and could see them literally sink or swim!</desc><sub-title>Amphicar</sub-title></programme></tv>