<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516131500 -0400" stop="20260516134500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Now that he's officially back at the precinct and desperate to solve a real case, Jake finds a loophole to get out of his temporarily designated desk duty. Unfortunately, that loophole rests on his ability to pass an official evaluation performed by Holt. While Charles provides Jake with moral support, Terry and Amy help Rosa, who believes Pimento may be cheating on her.</desc><sub-title>Kicks</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516133507 -0400" stop="20260516135850 -0400"><title>The Big Bang Theory</title><desc>Leonard volunteers to sign for a package in an attempt to make a good impression on Penny, but when he enlists Sheldon for help, his attempt at chivalry goes terribly awry.</desc><sub-title>The Big Bran Hypothesis</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516121839 -0400" stop="20260516140356 -0400"><title>Encanto</title><desc>An extraordinary family, the Madrigals, live hidden in the mountains of Colombia, in a magical house called an Encanto. The magic of the Encanto has blessed every child in the family with a unique gift - every child except one, Mirabel.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260516181500 +0100" stop="20260516190000 +0100"><title>House</title><desc>When it appears that Lucy Palmeiro, a schizophrenic mom with deep vein thrombosis, is lying about her alcohol intake, Dr. House is the lone voice of reason. Under the scrutiny of her hyper-vigilant teenage son, House takes Lucy off all her medications and secretly sends Foreman and Chase to search her apartment for clues.</desc><sub-title>The Socratic Method</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516131539 -0400" stop="20260516140252 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>Mike buys a supercar from the super saver menu. An Italian thoroughbred for under &#163;10k. But supercars mean super bills. Mike&#8217;s reports of wayward handling and a hair-trigger throttle could lead to either bankruptcy or a very nasty accident. Some of Edd&#8217;s smart solutions could help to keep the budget under control but will it be enough to tame this technology packed, turbocharged V8? Techy tyres help get the luxury GT powerhouse back on track and an overhauled air-conditioning system restores some Italian flair.</desc><sub-title>Maserati 3200GT</sub-title></programme></tv>