<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516223000 -0400" stop="20260516230000 -0400"><title>How I Met Your Mother</title><desc>When Robin fears that Barney is cheating on her, she soon discovers that he is spending his evenings with Ted learning everything there is to know on how to date her.</desc><sub-title>Robin 101</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516222348 -0400" stop="20260516224717 -0400"><title>Everybody Hates Chris</title><desc>When Chris's mother, Rochelle, hires the girl next door, Keisha, to tutor Drew at Math, Chris sees this as an ideal chance to impress her. But someone else may have the same intentions.   Meanwhile, Julius finds himself in an awkward position when he becomes attracted to another woman, Sheila.</desc><sub-title>Everybody Hates Keisha</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516211532 -0400" stop="20260516230555 -0400"><title>Moana</title><desc>In ancient Polynesia, when a terrible curse incurred by the demigod Maui reaches Moana's island, she answers the Ocean's call to seek out Maui to set things right.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517033000 +0100" stop="20260517040000 +0100"><title>The Simpsons</title><desc>Homer uses his medical insurance to buy Dimoxinil, a miracle hair-growth formula. After growing luxurious locks, he's given a promotion which allows him to hire a secretary named Karl and makes grand promises to his family at home.</desc><sub-title>Simpson and Delilah</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516220750 -0400" stop="20260516223515 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The competition begins at the Union Inn in Cowes on the Isle of Wight. The guests then head across the island to Shanklin where Andy Stein and Jo Rachy run the Shoreside Inn. A heated argument breaks out during the afternoon and breakfast leaves them cold.

The third visit is to Raj's Kirribilli Guesthouse in Newquay, Cornwall. Last is the Elysian Fields B&amp;B in Helston, Cornwall where Jackie Burchell showers her guests with gifts including personalised lollies.</desc><sub-title>From Union Inn to Elysian Fields</sub-title></programme></tv>