<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521090000 -0400" stop="20260521093000 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>Powers Brothers Aviation lands a huge government project and decides to let everyone have the day off and party at a bar. But George gets in trouble when he lets slip that Mel went to Vegas with Jack's ex-wife -- while they were still married! Geroge fears his firing, but is surprised to find out that Powers is splitting in two! Problems ensue when Mel offers George a job at the new design plant.</desc><sub-title>Split Decision</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521084620 -0400" stop="20260521102327 -0400"><title>Austin Powers in Goldmember</title><desc>The world's most shagadelic spy continues his fight against Dr. Evil. This time, the diabolical doctor and his clone, Mini-Me, team up with a new foe&#8212;'70s kingpin Goldmember. While pursuing the team of villains to stop them from world domination, Austin gets help from his dad and an old girlfriend.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521085454 -0400" stop="20260521102543 -0400"><title>Bo Burnham: Inside</title><desc>A musical comedy special shot and performed by Bo Burnham, alone, over the course of a very unusual year.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260521140000 +0100" stop="20260521150000 +0100"><title>Tipping Point</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 39</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521090015 -0400" stop="20260521095215 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>In the second hour of Ramsay's Great British Nightmare special Gordon visits The Runaway Girl. The kitchen does no preparation work before service, as Justin has had Richie pre-cook all the meals in advance to prevent wastage. Richie launches a heated tirade about Justin's inability to listen to criticism, threatening to resign if the restaurant does not immediately improve. Gordon employs a mystery diner to assess the service and despite Justin claiming to recognize their purpose, botches the service. After helping Justin and Richie make amends, he refurbishes the restaurant and renames it Silversmiths, bans live music and, realizing that they have no chance of competing against local Spanish restaurants, changes the focus to modern British cuisine. Before Gordon&#8217;s revisit, he sends another mystery diner to the restaurant, who gives a positive assessment of the service. Justin has stuck to the changes, and Richie has found a new passion for food.</desc><sub-title>The Runaway Girl</sub-title></programme></tv>