<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260524063000 -0400" stop="20260524070000 -0400"><title>Cheers</title><desc>Carla feels compelled to call in an exorcist when Eddie's ghost appears in the bar and Rebecca complains to a TV station about a defective hair removal system.</desc><sub-title>The Ghost and Mrs. Lebec</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260524061258 -0400" stop="20260524063802 -0400"><title>How I Met Your Mother</title><desc>Lily, Barney and Robin attend a high school prom to scout out a potential band for Lily and Marshall's wedding reception. In order to get in Lily and Robin pretend to be the dates of two kids who were going alone. Ted and Marshall are back at the apartment where they are preparing the invitations to be sent out.</desc><sub-title>Best Prom Ever</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260524050305 -0400" stop="20260524073312 -0400"><title>Jurassic World: Dominion</title><desc>After surviving the destruction of Isla Nubla, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing took in young Maisie Lockwood. They've been living under the radar to protect Maisie, but she feels like a prisoner. When Maisie goes missing, Owen and Claire set out to find her, and eventually confront Lewis Dodgson, owner of Biosyn. Paleobotanist Ellie Sattler, Paleontologist Alan Grant, and Chaotician Ian Malcolm set out to expose Dodgson's schemes.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260524110000 +0100" stop="20260524120000 +0100"><title>Clarkson's Farm</title><desc>Spring has sprung and rejuvinated Jeremy's farming the unfarmed idea, as he takes on multiple new projects to try and turn a profit from his unused land.. And there are some one week old arrivals to the farm to lift everyone's spirits.</desc><sub-title>Healing</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260524061603 -0400" stop="20260524064319 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>First up this week is luxury weight-loss and detox retreat Slimmeria, owned by Galia and Michael Grainger.

Health fanatic Galia's mission is to spread the Slimmeria message. But what do fun-loving Ann and Bill Clay from Bosvean House make of Galia's &#163;260 price tag, rules and regulations, and 9pm curfew?

Jan and William from St Giles are happy to comply, but Diane and Max from Ombersley Bed &amp; Breakfast suspect they're in for an uncomfortable night ahead when they sample the bed.

An afternoon work-out, Zumba-style, followed by a healthy meal and weight-loss lecture does little to get the party started.</desc><sub-title>Slimmeria Slimming Retreat, East Sussex</sub-title></programme></tv>