<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531183000 -0400" stop="20260531190000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>After Gene breaks his favorite, extremely rare '70s era Christmas record, Tina and Louise join him in the search for another copy. Meanwhile, Teddy wants to do a neighborhood Secret Santa with Bob and Linda.</desc><sub-title>Gene's Christmas Break</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531182623 -0400" stop="20260531185047 -0400"><title>Superstore</title><desc>The storewide heater malfunction magnifies angry tensions between Amy, Jonah and the back warehouse employees after both sides refuse to clean up a spill.  Meanwhile, Dina and Garrett find a way to pass the time and Cheyenne helps Glenn through an existential crisis as he tries to fix the heater himself.</desc><sub-title>Super Hot Store</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531175051 -0400" stop="20260531192826 -0400"><title>The Secret World of Arrietty</title><desc>The Clock family consists of three four-inch-tall people who live incognito among humans, borrowing only what they need to survive. Their quiet life changes when their teenage daughter, Arrietty, is discovered.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531233000 +0100" stop="20260601000000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Taffy has come in for a shift before taking his holidays.  He is worried he will miss his flight.  He tries to saw a bed rail to remove a prisoner but ends up removing the bed head instead.   Brownlow is trying to cut spending and tells Burnside that for the present they will have to use the buses.  Carver misses his on the way to a supermarket to see about staff pilfering.  He wrenches his ankle getting off the bus after a butcher smuggling meat out in his clothes.   Penny is going by the PACE book</desc><sub-title>Overspend</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531182100 -0400" stop="20260531184806 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The competition begins at Knockaloe Beg Farm in Peel on the Isle of Man. Here John and Fiona Anderson treat their guests to laser games, a trip around their farm and local produce.

The guests then head across the island to Port Erin where Phil Routledge runs the Arches B&amp;B.

The third visit is to Robbie and John Welling's The Trafford Hotel in Blackpool.

Last is Sheepy Lodge in Sheepy Magna, Warwickshire where Julie Brogan brought up her family and now fills it with paying guests.</desc><sub-title>From Knockaloe Beg Farm to Sheepy Lodge</sub-title></programme></tv>