<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260521174500 -0400" stop="20260521183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>Cuddy wants House to diagnose a psychiatrist who collapse at the South Pole. And she can't leave the station so House has to diagnose her via video link and she doesn't let House walk all over her, if anything she intrigues him. House is also frustrated that there's no longer any cable service and tries to get it restored. And when Wilson starts sneaking around and is being secretive House wonders why.</desc><sub-title>Frozen</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260521181232 -0400" stop="20260521183625 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>After George's warning about the evils of boys, Carmen comes home with a hickey; Ernie uses Max to meet single moms.</desc><sub-title>Love Bites</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260521181517 -0400" stop="20260521201346 -0400"><title>Raiders of the Lost Ark</title><desc>When Dr. Indiana Jones &#8211; the tweed-suited professor who just happens to be a celebrated archaeologist &#8211; is hired by the government to locate the legendary Ark of the Covenant, he finds himself up against the entire Nazi regime.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260521230000 +0100" stop="20260521233000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>An Italian turns up at the front desk asking for directions to the Blackball tunnell.   Viv comes across a burglar with a gun who knocks her down and takes off.  He was trying to break into a whole food warehouse.  At the end of her shift he wants to apologise to her.   Ramsey goes to a girlfriend's house to dry his trousers and gets to a riot at a party late where 2 people are arrested.  When the sister of one comes to complain, Tosh sends a robot, with a policeman's hat on, out to talk to her.</desc><sub-title>No Shelter</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260521174303 -0400" stop="20260521182914 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Actress Rebel Wilson joins Keegan-Michael Key to explore the power of the subconscious when it comes to falling in love.</desc><sub-title>Rebel Wilson: Love and Attraction</sub-title></programme></tv>