<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530214800 -0400" stop="20260530220000 -0400"><title>Hot Package</title><desc>With Pat O'Brien on vacation, Mark McGrath fills in as Derrick's cohost. But things go awry when Hollywood goes on strike, and a disgruntled millitant holds the studio hostage. The show draws to a dramatic conclusion, and someone dies.</desc><sub-title>A Brand New Day</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530212339 -0400" stop="20260530215557 -0400"><title>Last Week Tonight with John Oliver</title><desc>Last Week Tonight Tackles U.S. Primaries and Caucuses: The United States selection process for presidential nominees is convoluted &#8212; to say the least. Nevertheless, John Oliver reminds Americans that the "middle of the game" is the worst possible time to change the rules.</desc><sub-title>Primaries and Caucuses</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530210133 -0400" stop="20260530223455 -0400"><title>Final Destination 2</title><desc>When Kimberly has a violent premonition of a highway pileup she blocks the freeway, keeping a few others meant to die, safe...Or are they? The survivors mysteriously start dying and it's up to Kimberly to stop it before she's next.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531023000 +0100" stop="20260531030000 +0100"><title>Friends</title><desc>The gang heads over to London for Ross and Emily's wedding. Joey can't contain his excitement about London which annoys Chandler to no end and results in two of them arguing. While the guys are touring the city, Monica, together with Ross and Emily, visit the chapel where the wedding ceremony is supposed to take place only to find out that it's being torn down prematurely.

Phoebe tries to warn the gang that Rachel is coming to London to tell Ross that she still loves him. After the initial excitement about visiting England dissipates, Joey begins to feel homesick, however, one of the bridesmaids helps him to forget about it. Meanwhile, Ross and Emily's parents get into an argument over the bill for the wedding.</desc><sub-title>The One with Ross's Wedding</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530214638 -0400" stop="20260530221434 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The final day of the competition is at Heyford House in Lower Heyford, Oxfordshire, owned by veterans of the hospitality trade, Leo and Sonya Brooke-Little.

The afternoon event is boxing, which Brock sees as a perfect opportunity to settle some scores with Dave and Alan.</desc><sub-title>Heyford House</sub-title></programme></tv>