<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517170000 -0400" stop="20260517174500 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>Based on practically no information and no medical history about a mystery patient sent by the CIA, House is using some unorthodox methods to diagnose and treat him. Meanwhile the remaining candidates are questioning Foreman's judgment.</desc><sub-title>Whatever It Takes</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517172027 -0400" stop="20260517174558 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>A Major Crimes detective known as "The Vulture" takes over Jake's nearly solved case and steals his thunder, prompting revenge.</desc><sub-title>The Vulture</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517153428 -0400" stop="20260517175744 -0400"><title>Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith</title><desc>As the Clone Wars nears its end, Obi-Wan Kenobi pursues a new threat, while Anakin Skywalker is lured by Chancellor Palpatine into a sinister plot for galactic domination.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517221500 +0100" stop="20260517224500 +0100"><title>Friends</title><desc>Monica considers a dream job as head chef in Pete's new restaurant, but Phoebe fears there is more to the deal. Ross makes a sacrifice to help Rachel, who may have a broken rib. Meanwhile, Joey buys Chandler an unusual pet.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Chick and the Duck</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517164921 -0400" stop="20260517174104 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>The new series of Ramsay&#8217;s Kitchen Nightmares hits the ground running as Gordon comes to the aid of resting actor Allan Love.  Despite an aversion to fish Allan opened Ruby Tates, a high end seafood restaurant in Brighton. But it hasn&#8217;t been a success. Thanks to a pair of lazy chefs producing badly cooked, poor quality food at premium prices Ruby Tates is losing &#163;1500 a week.  And it&#8217;s not just the food that&#8217;s off-putting. The restaurant&#8217;s name is instantly forgettable, even to locals and the d&#233;cor, featuring a paint splattered pair of knickers, is keeping potential punters far from the door.</desc><sub-title>Ruby Tates</sub-title></programme></tv>